Previously on desperate housewives...
前情回顾
you're glowing today,you know that?
你今天看上去真靓！
Gabrielle got pregnant...
Gabrielle怀孕了
You walked out on me
是你抛弃了我
Yeah,but look how far I got
看看我现在的日子
I'm just up the street
Trouble moved in...
困惑开始了...
being with george made youfeel a bit guilty.
同george在一起让你感到内疚
Well,I'll just have to get over it,won't I?
但是我必须得忘却这一切 不是吗？
And bree moved on...
Bree开始了新生活...
"I know who really killed Melanie Foster
我知道是谁杀死了melanie foster
"You arrested the wrong man"?
你们抓错人了
But not everyone...
但不是人人...
you got a killer locked up in the basement
告诉他们地下室里关着个杀人犯
He is not a killer.
他不是杀人犯
Got what they deserved.
...都得到应得的
It is often said that necessity is the mother of invention.
常言道 需要是创造之母
This is how mothers came to invent play dates--
所以母亲们才想出了玩伴这个主意
so they occasionally could have a little time for themselves.
这样他们就能有点属于自己的时间
If you need me,I'll be at the salon.
有事去发廊找我
But there are some mothers
不过有些母亲没法 享受这一创造带来了快乐
who don't get to take advantage of this maternal innovation--
mothers like lynette scavo,
比如lynette scavo
who was no longer able to rest on weekends
她即使到了周末也没法休息
because her twins no longer received play date invitations,
因为她的双胞胎儿子没有自己的玩伴
ever since they had convinced sasha eden's boy
因为他们俩曾经对sasha eden的儿子说
that a pair of magic wings would allow him to fly.
一对有魔法的翅膀能让他飞起来
And they had double-dared sharon chazin's boy
因为他们曾让sharon chazin的 儿子蒙着眼睛骑自行车
to ride his bike blindfolded.
And they had encouraged lisa siegmann's boy
因为他们怂恿lisa siegmann的儿子 玩一个叫做“扔砖头”的新游戏
to try an exciting new game called "toss the brick."
The scavo twins had become persona non grata,
Scavo家的双胞胎成了不受欢迎的人
of being able to take an occasional nap on saturdays
而lynette周六能偶尔打个盹的 梦想则变得越来越渺茫
was growing dimmer and dimmer...
until one day...
直到有一天...
hey,hey,hey,hey!Porter,preston,knock it off!
嘿 嘿 嘿 嘿 Porter preston 别打了！
All right? Did you hear me?I said stop it. Stand up.
没听见我说话吗？别打了！站起来！
Stand up. Come here.
站起来 到这来
I'm so sorry.Did my son beat you up?
对不起 我儿子打你了吗？
No. We were beating them up.
没有 我们在打他
Is that true?Did they beat you up?
真的？他们在打你？
Ah,it didn't hurt that much.
恩 一点不疼
Jimmy,P.J.,What are you doing?
Jimmy, P.J. 你们在干吗？
What have I told you about ganging up on people?
说过多少次了不可以打架！
I am so sorry.
对不起
No,it's okay.You know,believe me,
没关系
my boys can take careof themselves.
我儿子自己能管好自己
If they got hurt at all,I'll pay for the doctor bills.
如果他们哪受伤了 我来付医药费
No,not to worry.
不用了 别担心
I got the feeling they were sort of enjoying themselves.
我倒觉得他们很玩的来
Really?
真的？
What would you say to bringing your boys over to my house
要不以后你们把孩子带到我家来 有空一起和我儿子玩玩？
and letting them hang out with mine sometime?
And that's how lynette finally got what she needed--
Lynette现在终于得到她一直梦寐以求的
time for herself...
属于自己的时间
and play dates for her kids...
还为自己孩子找到了玩伴...
I'm sorry,
不好意思 我儿子和你们孩子打石头仗了
but my boys decided to have a rock fight with your boys.
It was fun!
好好玩啊！
Play dates she was determined to keep...
几位她不愿意放弃的玩伴
well,they look fine to me.
呃 我看没什么事
At all costs.
不顾一切
Same time next week?
下周同一时间？
Okay.
好的
Sync: YTET-Starry -==www.ydy.com/bbs==-
-=伊甸园论坛 http://www.ydy.com=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
Desperate Housewives Season 2 Episode 7
Cameras are simple tools designed to capture images--
-=COSL-YTET小组工作室=- 照相机是用来拍摄记录的
images that tell us more about ourselves than we realized
翻译: 少数派 Maggiezl 那些照片能告诉我们很多
They remind us of the long journey we've taken
校对: 少数派 Ronald 它们能让我们想起曾经一起走过的路
the loved ones who traveled alongside us...
想起陪伴在身边的至爱之人
those we lost along the way...
想起同行中离我们而去的人
and those waiting for us on the road ahead
还有那些在前方等待我们的人
Okay.
有张子宫图在眼前晃悠 我怎么吃的下？
a uterus staring me in the face?
Oh,gaby,I didn't know you got a sonogram
哦 Gabby 我们都不知道你去做过B超了
Let me see. Oh.
让我看看
Honey,you need to put that in a frame or something
最好给照片镶个框
I don't think so.
我才不呢
Oh,come on. That's a picture of your baby
别这样 那可是你孩子的照片
You can't tell me you're not a little bit excited
你不可能一点都不兴奋吧
Fine. I'm pregnant. Whee!
好吧 我怀孕咯 哈哈哈
Now come on.
别说这个了 我们来是要安慰Susan的
We're supposed to be cheering up susan.
This is a time of crisis,
现在是危机时刻
and I think you need another scoop of mint chocolate chip
给你再来一勺薄荷冰淇淋
Thanks.
谢谢
Susan,why are you so eerily calm?
Susan 你怎么出奇地冷静？
Mike delfino just dumped you.
Mike delfino刚刚甩了你
The susan mayer I know would be a...
我所认识的susan mayer 现在应该痛哭流涕才对呀
...blubbering mess right now.
Oh,come on. Trot her on out.
给我们讲讲嘛
She's fun to watch.
看她这样真有意思
Actually,I think I'm starting to feel pretty zen
其实我倒觉得这事应该看开一点
about the whole thing.
Well,I think mike will calm down
Mike需要冷静一下 过几天他应该会明白的
in a  couple of days and come to his senses.
No. I came between the man and his son
不是 我阻碍一个男人和他的儿子见面
It was a huge betrayal.
这简直是天大的背叛
I can't even blame him for hating me
他这么恨我 我不怪他
But zach was starting to obsess with julie again
但是zach又那么迷恋julie
Exactly. You're a mother tring to protect her child
是呀 身为人母 保护自己的孩子
It's a natural impulse.
是母性的本能
Over the past couple of days,
这几天
I gave myself a long,hard look in the mirror
我自己也好好照了照镜子
and I did not like what I saw.
实在不喜欢现在这副嘴脸
I'm with you. Carry on.
我支持你 继续！
I just think if I start acting like an adult for once
我只是想如果我表现的成熟稳重一点
maybe... who knows?
也许...谁又知道呢？
Somewhere down the line,
以后mike和我至少能作个朋友吧
mike and I at least can be friends
All right,you're not zen.
说了这么半天 你这哪是看开了
You're numb.
分明是受刺激变麻木了嘛
I'm fine.
我没事
Do you got any pie?
有派吃吗？
Not unless we make some.
没做
I can wait.
我可以等
so if you need us,
如果你们有事找我们
we'll be at home,
就去我们家 反正在家闲着没事
just having a quiet evening.
funny. We're expecting quite the opposite
有意思 我们这可热闹呢
Well,don't forget,next week it's our turn
呃 别忘了 下周轮到我们带孩子
We'll be taking porter and...
我们整个周末会好好 看管porter和Preston
- preston. - Preston off your hands all weekend
Rest assured,we have not forgotten
放心 我们没忘
See ya.
回见
don't worry.
别担心
Whoa,guys.
嘿 小家伙们
Whoa,why aren't you upstairs with P.J and Jimmy?
嘿 小家伙们 你们怎么 不和P.J.和jimmy在一起？
They're watching this dumb video they brought
他们在看带过来什么录像带
It's boring.
好无聊啊
Well,you should be polite and watch it,too
那你们应该懂礼貌和他们一起看呀
You know,they're our guests
他们可是我们家的客人
Guys.
小家伙们
hey,guys,we have snacks.
嘿 小家伙们 上点心咯
fix the light,
调好灯光 我们就可以了
then we're good to go.
- Okay,ready? - Okay
好了 可以开始了吗？ 好的
All right,hang on now.
好了 等一下
Guys,what is this?
你们在看什么？
A movie.
电影
Mommy and daddy made it.
爸妈自拍的
Whoa. What's under there?
哇 下面是什么？
Peekaboo. Peekaboo.
偷偷看 偷偷看
oh,my god! Oh,my god!
哦 天啊 天啊
Where's the "off" button?
开关在哪里啊？
It's underneath the panel thing
下面， 面板那个位置
Well,it's stuck,it's stuck.
卡住了 卡住了
Get the remote. Get the remote.
遥控器 快拿遥控器
What's wrong?
怎么了？
I found it.
我找到了
So can we have the cocoa now?
我们能喝可口可乐吗？
Well,what do you think?
你怎么看？
It is glorious.
真好看
I have to have it.
就要它了
I'm not sure you deserve Dolce & gabbana
不知道你是否该穿dolce & gabbana （意大利著名服装品牌）
Vern.
Vern
You never call. You never write
你不打电话，也不写信
I know I haven't been in the store lately
我知道最近没来光顾
but I've been a little busy
但我一直忙着把我丈夫弄出监狱
getting my husband out of jail.
That is such a write trash thing to say
真可怜啊
Luckily,the judge dropped the hate crime charge
好在法官没有追究仇恨犯罪
so now all carlos has to do is
好在法官没有追究仇恨犯罪 Carlos只要服完劳役即可
serve out the slave labor thing.
Carlos只要服完劳役即可
He'll be out in six months.
六个月后就刑满释放了
If he's still in the hoosegow,
他既然还在坐牢 你还需要这么花哨的衣服干吗？
why do you need a fancy party dress?
Because some of my model friends
因为周六有几个纽约来的模特朋友来看我
are coming down from new york on friday,
so I have to look better than ever.
我得看上去光彩照人才行
I can't have 'em thinking I moved to the suburbs
我可不能让他们看出来 我搬到了市郊后就在大卖场买衣服
and now I shop at strip malls.
But when they see this dress, they will crumple to the floor
但是她们要是看到你这身衣服 肯定要惊叹得拜倒在地呀
like the botoxed hags they are.
Good
很好 衣服好像有点紧
you know,it's a little snug.
Yeah,I see that. I have the same thing in a zero.
我也看出来了 不过这款衣服还有别的尺寸
Why not go up a size?
换大一号的试试吧
Because I wear double zero,you twerp.
我就要穿小号的 笨蛋！
Why you getting snippy?
Because you just called me fat.
因为你刚刚说我胖了
Honey,you're pregnant.Your body's changing.
哦 你怀孕了 身体自然发生了变化
But I'm only three months pregnant.
可是我才三个月啊 三个月肚子没那么大啊
Women don't show at three months.
Some women do.
有些人三个月肚子很大了
Do you want the larger sizeor not?
还要不要大号的了？
I'm just not gonna eat for two days.
那我干脆两天不吃饭
okay,you totally deserve to wear dolce & gabbana.
好吧 你可以穿dolce & gabbana了
I want an explanation,karl.
我需要你解释 karl
Do you hear me?
听到没有？
Edie,you just better get the hell off my back,
Edie 你最好别来烦我，否则我就
Oh,what are you gonna do? I'd like to hear this.
哦 你就干吗？我倒想听听
The big man with the big threats.
这么大块头就会动动嘴皮子威胁啊？
Back off.Just back the hell off.
别烦我 别烦我
Okay,so I got the box of things you left on my porch.
你留在门外的盒子我拿到了
Yeah,I figured you'd want your stuff back.
我想你需要拿回自己的东西
Thanks. That's great,
谢谢
'cause if you decided to hang onto my joni mitchell cds,
如果你还扣着我的 joni mitchell的CD不放 （加拿大著名女歌手）
I would have had to come after you with a club.
恐怕我得拿着棍棒追赶着你要了
you're right.It's not funny.
没错 一点不好笑
Actually,I did want to just see if you were aware that you
其实我来是想问问你知不知道
gave me backthe valentine's day card I made you
你把那张我给你做的 情人节贺卡也退了回来
I was aware,yeah.
我知道
Oh. Well,I mean,when two people split up,
其实两人分手一般不会 退回情人节贺卡之类的东西
normally they don't give things back
like valentine's day cards.
其实两人分手一般不会 退回情人节贺卡之类的东西
If you don't want it,you can throw it away.
你不想要的话 完全可以扔了
Just please don't give it back to me. It's tacky.
就是别退给我 样子实在不怎么样
I'm sorry.
不好意思 是人都会犯...错误
That's okay.People make... mistakes.
Anything else?
还有什么事吗？
Look,are you sure this is what you want to do?
你真的决意和我分手？
I mean,I understand
我知道你不想继续我们的关系 你说的很明白
that you don't want our relationship to continue.
You have made that clear,but...
我知道你不想继续我们的关系 你说的很明白
I sort of thought down the long corridors of time,
但是我在想也许今后我们还可以做朋友
maybe you and I could be friends,
and if you keep acting like this--
可如果你一直这样子
susan,it's over on every level,okay? I...
Susan 我们结束了 彻底结束了 明白吗？
I've moved on.You should do the same.
我会开始新的生活 你也应该如此
miserable son of a bitch!
你可恶的混蛋！
I'm a hell of a lot betterat keeping them than you are!
如果我要是有什么秘密 我绝对比你能保守秘密
well,I'll say one thing for us.
不过我们之间倒有件事值得一说
Even with all our problems,
尽管我们问题多多 可我们至少没象他们那样
at least we're not acting like that.
Okay,I'm starting to get the feeling
好吧 我怎么感觉
that we're not going to a yard sale.
我们不是去旧货甩卖场？
That was just a clever ruse to get you into my car.
那只是让你上车的借口
Are you ready for your surprise?
准备好看我给你的惊喜了吗？
Mm-hmm.
恩
Oh.
哦
George,this is just an empty house.
George 这只不过是间空房子
Why is this a surprise?
有什么好惊喜的？
I just bought it.
我刚买的
Oh,my god! Congratulations.
哦 天啊 恭喜你了
Oh,george,I didn't even know you were looking.
哦 george 我都不知道你一直在看房子
Hurry,ceal. They're here!
快点 ceal 他们来了
I'm coming.Hey,georgie.
我来了 嘿 George
Bree,I'd like you to meet my mother.
Bree 这位是我母亲
George never introduces me to anyone.
George从没象我介绍过外人
So I knew you were special.
所以我知道你一定与众不同
And this is ceal,my mother's friend,
这位是Ceal 我母亲的朋友
and the real estate agent who sold me the house.
她就是卖这座房子的房地产经纪人
Hi.
嘿
Well,we're gonna go in the back
我们还是去后面吧
so george can,you know...
这样你们俩就能...
so...
你...
do you really like it?
喜欢吗？
I do. I really do.
喜欢 真的喜欢
Good,'cause I was sort of hoping that...
太好了 因为我打算...
you might like to live here.
让你住在这里
Bree...
will you marry me?
愿意嫁给我吗？
Huh?
呃？
I love you,
我爱你
and I think I know how you feel about me, so why wait?
我也知道你的感受 干吗还要等呢？
George,rex hasn't even been dead for two months.
George，Rex去世才两个月啊
Yes,but if his death has taught us anything,
没错 但是他去世也深深地教育了我们
it's that life is short.It's dumb to play it safe.
那就是生命是短暂的 谨慎行事有时很傻的
If we see a chance for happiness,
如果我们看到了幸福的机遇
we should grab it and hold on tight.
我们应该抓住不放
See,I thought we were going to a yard sale.
我以为我们是去旧货甩卖场
Please. Just say the word,
求你了 答应吧
and you'll make methe happiest guy on earth.
我就是世界上最幸福的男人了
congratulations,you two.
恭喜两位！
Mazel tov.
Mazel tov（希伯莱语：好运）
Guys,wait.She hasn't said yes yet.
等等 她还没答应呢
Oh.
哦
I told you we should wait.
我说要再等等吧
Um... so,uh,bree...
呃... 呃 bree...
what do you say?
你看如何？
See,george,um,the thing is...
george 呃 其实...
okay.
我愿意
You will?
你愿意？
You'll marry me?
你愿意嫁给我？
Okay.
是的
oh!
哦
oh,my baby!
哦 我的孩子
Who is it?
哪位？
It's your ex-husband.
你的前夫？
Oh. Karl.
哦 Karl
What do you want?
有什么事？
Edie and I just broke up.
Edie和我刚刚分手
Oh. Well,come on in.
哦 进来吧
Sorry to come over on such short notice,
不好意思这么突然
but I couldn't face going to a motel.
但我又不愿意去旅馆住
That's okay. Julie's staying at a friend's tonight.
没事 Julie反正去朋友家了
You can sleep in her room.
你可以睡在她屋里
Well,the sofa's fine,but thanks.
沙发就可以了 不过谢谢你
So am I allowed to ask what happened?
那么我能问问出什么事了吗？
You could ask,but I won't tell.
可以问 但我不会告诉你的
- Why not?
- 为什么？
'Cause it's embarrassing.
因为说出来丢人现眼的
Karl,did you cheat again?
Karl 你是不是在外面又有女人了？
No.
没有
Did she cheat?
那她在外面有别的男人了？
No
也没有
You finally saw her without her makeup.
你终于看到她卸妆后的样子了
- Susan...
I'm sorry
不好意思
Are you okay?
你没事吧？
Yeah. It hadn't been working for quite a while.
恩 其实这么长时间来一直不顺畅
This was inevitable.
发生这事也在所难免
Well,these days,
如今
anybody going through a breakup gets my sympathy.
谁分手了 我都同情
That's right. I heard you made the plumber angry.
没错 听说你惹火了那个水管工
No,I made the plumber furious,
不是 我是惹怒了他
and it's definitely over.
彻底结束了
So there will be no gloating from me.
所以你分手 我不会沾沾自喜了
Well,here's to no gloating.
那就敬一杯
mm. Actually,I'm trying to keep a positive outlook
其实我一直想就这事
on the whole thing. um..
保持乐观态度 呃..
last night,I started writing,and...
昨天晚上 我就动笔写了写 呃...
well,I think there's a book in there.
我想完全可以写本书出来
- A book?
- 书？
Yeah.
是的
Like one of your children's books?
儿童读物？
No. This one's for adults,
不 是给成年人看的
about all my failed relationships.
关于我失败的恋爱和婚姻
You're not writing about me,are you?
你不会在写我吧？
You're like the first 14 chapters.
你可能得占据前14章
Are you gonna be fair?
写的时候公正吗？
I'm gonna be honest.
我会实话实说的
I was afraid of that.
我就怕那个
it was just awful.
当时太尴尬了
George had a ring.
George手里拿着戒指
His mother and her friend were there with champagne.
他母亲和朋友端着香槟
If I had said "no,"it would have devastated him.
我要是说“不愿意” 肯定对他造成打击
So you agreed to marry him just to be polite?
你同意嫁给他就是出于礼貌原因？
Well,obviously,
呃 很明显
there's a downside to having good manners.
有时过于礼貌也不好啊
So when will you tell him how you really feel?
那么你打算什么时候 告诉他你的真实感受？
That's why I wanted to talk to you.
所以我才来找你啊
I mean,part of me
我一边
keeps thingking maybe I should just do it.
在想就这么做
Do it?You mean actually marry him?
做？你是说真的要嫁给他？
Well,I know it sounds rash,but...
我也知道这显得很鲁莽 但是...
well,there's something comfortable about george.
和george在一起感觉很舒服
We share the same tastes and interests.
我们趣味相投
Oh,and best of all,he loves the opera.
而且他喜欢歌剧
The opera?
歌剧？
Yes,we saw "aida" last week, and we both cried buckets
是的 上周我们看了《阿依达》 我们都哭成一团了
It was fun.
真有意思
George loves art,poetry and music.
George热爱艺术 诗歌和音乐
It would be nice to be married to someone who
能嫁给一个象我这样
looks for beauty in the world like I do.
寻找生活中的美的男人真的很好
I don't know.That's why I'm here.
我也迷惑了 所以我才来找你
I don't know what to do,dr. Goldfine.
我也不知道该怎么办 Goldfine医生
Bree,you've said many times
Bree 你多次提到
how comfortable you are with george,
和george在一起是多么的舒服
but you don't feel for him the way you felt for rex.
但是你对他的感觉 不是你对rex的那种感觉？
No.
是的
True love is great.
真爱的确可贵
But at this point in my life,
但我现在这样
I think I'd rather just go to the opera.
我宁愿去看歌剧
Give me your glass
把被子给我
-We gotta finish off this.
-我们得喝光了
Oh,no,no,wait
不 不 别
No way,no way,no way. Four glasses is my limit.
不行 不行 我顶多喝四杯
If you help me finish off this bottle,
如果你能帮我喝光这瓶酒
I'll tell you what happened between me and edie.
我酒告诉你我和edie究竟出什么事了
Hit me.
那就来吧
edie was making the bed
edie正在铺床
and found a picture I kept under the mattress--
找到了一张我放在床垫下的照片--
a picture I didn't want her to see.
我不想让她看见的一张照片
What was it?
谁的照片？
It was a picture of you.
你的照片
Why would you...
你为什么...
because it's something I like to take a look at
因为我想
every now and then.
时不时地看看
- what the hell was that?
- 你干吗这样？
That was something
其实
I've been wanting to do for quite some time.
我很久以来一直想这么做
Oh,that's just you're bounding from edie.
哦 你只是在分手恢复期
So you're on the rebound from the plumber.
你不也是嘛
No harm,no foul.
不会有事 也没“违规”
Karl,it would be so weird.
Karl 这样感觉太怪了
We're two old friends who suddenly find themselves single.
我们只是两位突然发现 自己又单身了的老朋友
There's nothing weird about us
没什么奇怪的
helping each other out to be...
互相帮助...
a little less lonely.
摆脱寂寞而已
Thanks so much for taking care of the boys.
十分感谢你们照顾我的孩子
I'll be back on friday to pick your guys up.
我周五过来接你们的孩子
Leonard and I are gonna take them all to the water park.
Leonard和我会带她们去水上公园玩
Yeah,um,before that happens...
呃 走之前...
and we're gonna be able to take penny soon, aren't we?
我们很快就能接走penny 对吗？
She's getting so big
她长起来可快了
peekaboo.
偷偷看
Peekaboo. Peekaboo.
偷偷看 偷偷看
Yeah,okay,enough of that
好了 够了！
is there something wrong?
怎么了？
Actually,yes.
其实 我们有事
We've agonized whether to tell you this, norma,but...
我们一直在犹豫是否应该告诉你...
one of your...private videos
你们自己录制的录像带有一盘
made its way into jimmy and P.J.'S bag.
跑到jimmy和P.J.的书包里去了
Please... tell me the kids didn't see it.
他们没看吧？
Oh,no,don't worry.I caught it,I caught it...
哦 没事 我及时发现阻止了...
right before you took off your bra.
就在你脱下胸罩前
I have to go.
我得走了
Oh,norma. It's okay.
哦 norma 没事的
We just thought you needed to know what happened.
我们只是想让你知道发生的事
Seriously,we're cool with it
其实我们没什么意见
so long as you keep it away from the kids
只是不想让孩子看见
I told leonard this was gonna happen!
我跟leonard说过迟早要出事
Jimmy,P.J.,Close the door! Are we all buckled up?!
Jimmy,P.J.关上门 系好安全带
Norma,wait!
Norma 等等
We're still on for next week!
下周你们得来啊
Norma! The water park!
Norma! 水上公园！
Right?
是吧？
Mom!
妈
Mom?
妈？
Mom,are you up?
妈 起床了吗？
Mom--
妈--
oh,my god.
哦 天啊
Oh. Julie! I thought you were going straight to school.
哦 Julie! 我以为你直接去上学了
I-I needed money for lunch.
我得要买午饭的钱
There's a $20 in my pants... if you can find 'em.
我裤子口袋里有20块... 看能不能找得到了
Oh,uh,julie,uh...
哦 呃 julie 呃...
oh,julie,uh...honey.
Okay,there is a good explanation for what happened.
我可以解释
I doubt that.
我深表怀疑
You probably don't know that your father and edie
你不知道你爸爸和edie
broke up last night.
昨晚分手了
You slept with him the same night he broke up with her.
他分手的当晚你就和他睡在了一起
Well,I said it was a good explanation, not a great one.
我说了可以解释 没说可以解释通
oh,julie.
哦 julie
- Hey,pumpkin.
- 宝贝 早
Don't even
别说
oh,now I feel really awful.
真够尴尬的
Me too.
是呀
We should not have done what we did.
昨晚我们不应该那么做
I know,I know.
我也知道
But I gotta tell you,
但不管怎么说
last night was the best sex ever.
昨晚做爱真棒
Wasn't it,though?You were fantastic.
是嘛？你也不赖
Hey,I was just trying to keep up with you.
我当时只是想跟着你的节奏
Why do you think we got so good all of a sudden?
你觉得我们为什么突然好起来？
Because we've been angry at each other for so long,
因为我们以前一直恶言相赠
and we finally found a way to channel it.
现在终于找到疏通的机会了
Maybe.
也许吧
So what happens next?
下面该怎么办？
Well,I'm gonna take a shower.
我先洗个澡
No,I-I mean with us.
不是 我是说我们俩
Us? What do you mean?There's no us.
我们？什么意思？没有什么“我们”
You can't tell me you can just walk away
你不会想就这么了事吧
from this chemistry we got goin'.
我们关系可刚刚好起来
I mean,what happened last night was...
要知道昨晚可是...
whew. Explosive.
十分火爆啊
Karl,last night was two old friends
Karl 昨晚只不过是两个老朋友
helping each other through a rough patch. That's it.
互度难关而已 没什么
Susie Q...
karl,I want to move on.I don't want to go backwards.
karl 我要继续生活下去 我可不想走回头路
I'm sorry
不好意思
But thanks for the explosion
但是谢谢你的“火爆”
I really needed it.
我很需要
After 48 hours of crash dieting,
在48小时的减肥餐后,
gabrielle prepared to savor the fruit of her labor.
gabrielle准备展现一下她的劳动成果.
But she was dismayed to discover that she herself
但是她很沮丧地发现她自己...
had ripened considerably.
显然胖了许多
ohh!
噢!
ralph!
Ralph!
I need help getting dressed.Get in here!
我需要人帮我把衣服穿上   进来!
Now!
就现在!
I have to fit in this,so for god's sakes,
我必须要穿上它
put some muscle into it.
你使点劲
I'm trying.
我在试...
It won't zip.
拉链拉不上
Well,try harder.
哦,再用力点
Ohh! Ow. My hands hurt.
噢! 弄痛我手了
I'm sorry,ms. Solis,but ican't get you into this dress.
对不起,Solis夫人,我没法帮你穿上它
It's just too small.
它实在是太小了
Get me into this dress,
帮我穿上它,
and I will pay you $10 more a week.
每星期我再加你10美元工资
I think I got it. Hold on.Hold still. Here we go.
我想我可以了 憋住气 别动 开始
One...
一...
two...
二...
three. There.
三. 好了
Ohh! Thank god.
噢! 谢天谢地
we brought you some ice cream.
我们给你带了些冰淇淋
I know how long it's been since you had any.
我知道你已经好久没吃了
We'll have that in a minute,sweetheart.
再一会,我们就可以吃了 甜心
First,I want youto talk to me
首先,我想跟你谈谈
about what happened...
关于melanie...
about melanie.
到底发生了什么
I don't want to talk about her.
我不想跟你谈她
You know it breaks my heart to keep you down here like this.
你知不知道这样关着你让我很难过
But I can't let you out until I am positive
但是我不能让你出去,直到我确信...
that you will never hurt anyone else again.
你不会伤害任何人
And the first step
但是第一步
is for you to show me that you understand
你必须让我看到你明白
that what you did was wrong.
你所做的一切都是错的
She was a bad person.
她不是一个好人
She deserved it.
她活该
No one deserves to die like that,caleb.
没人应该像那样死去,caleb
Don't you agree?
难道你不这么认为?
Very well.
很好
If that's how it's going to be...
如果你坚持事情这样发展的话...
this is how it's going to be.
那我也会坚持
I can't believe we're doing this.
我简直不相信我们要这样做
If leonard and norma want to cut ties with us,
如果leonard和norma想和我们断绝来往,
who are we to stop them?
我们凭什么要来阻止他们?
They need to know we don't judge them
他们应该要明白我们并不想评论
for what they do in the privacy of their own home.
他们在自己家这干了什么事
And,well,it's not unheard of to tape yourself
而且,在做爱时把自己录下来
while you're having sex.
并不是什么耸人听闻的事
Well,obviously,there were so embarrassed,
可是,很显然,这多么尴尬,
they don't want anythingt o do with us.
他们并不想我们做任何事
Maybe we need to respect that.
也许我们应该尊重他们
I need these play dates
我需要他们家的玩伴
tom,we need these play dates
tom,我们需要给孩子找个玩伴
Fine. Fine.But you do all the talking.
好 好 但是你来说
Okay.
行
- Norma...
Aah!
噢!
Wait!
等等!
- Let's go.
- 我们走吧
No!
不!
Hey,scavos.What are you guys doing here?
嘿,scavos.你们来这干吗?
Hi. Sorry for just showing up unannounced, but,um...
嘿 很抱歉突然到访, 但是...
could we talk to you for a minute?
我们能和你谈一下吗?
Sure,come on in.
当然,请进
so,um,
这样的,呃,
we've been trying to contact you,
我们试着想要跟你们联系,
but you haven't been returning any of our messages.
可你们没回复我们的消息
And we really hope it isn't because of the porno video.
我们真的希望不是那个色情带子的原因
Home--home movies.
家庭--家庭电影
The fact is,we really don't care,
事实是,我们并不是很在意,
and it's certainly no reason to keep our boys apart.
而且也没有理由让我们的孩子不见面呀
We just don't know how they found it.
我们真的不知道他们是怎么找到的
But you know boys--they get into everything,
但是你知道孩子--他们对任何事都好奇,
but seriously,it's not a big deal.
但严格来说,这也不是什么大事情
I mean,just as long as you make sure it never happens again.
我的意思是,只要你们保证它不再发生
It's the new millennium.We're--we're hip.
现在是新时代了 我们--我们都很时髦...
You know,what we're saying is,we get it.
你明白,我们要说的是,我们明白
You're just having fun.It's nothing to be ashamed of.
你们只是在寻乐  没什么好感到羞耻的
I'm just so relieved this all worked out.
这件事能解决,我真的感到很轻松
At one point we actually talked
前一阵子我们还讨论过
about selling the house and moving.
是否要卖掉房子 搬走
Oh,no!
哦,不!
thank you for being so open-minded.
感谢你能那么开明
Please,we're all adults.It'S...
不必,我们都是成人了 这...
I gotta tell you,the most embrarrassing part of that video
我想说的是,这个录象最尴尬的部分是...
is how poorly it was shot.
它拍得很糟
The production valuesare ca-ca.
拍摄毫无价值
Well,from a lay perspective, it looked very professional.
哦,从外人看来 很专业呀
What you saw was an example of my earlier work.
你们所看到的只是我一个早期作品
Since then I've become much more adept at... production.
从那时侯开始,我对摄影很...在行
Ah.
哦
You know,editing and lighting.
你知道,导演和灯光
Leonard has always dreamed of directing movies.
Leonard 一直想要拍摄一部电影
Ironic,isn't it?I finally get my wish
很讽刺,是不是?我最终实现了我的愿望
and no one ever gets to see my work.
但没人会看到我的作品
That is a damn shame.
简直可惜了
Norma,what do you think? Should we show them the room?
Norma,你觉得呢? 应该让他们看看我们的房间吗?
Let's show 'em the room.Huh?
让他们看看我们的房间
Check out this baby.3-chip high-def,
看看这些小玩意 3芯片的 高清晰,
1280x720 lines of resolution, bounced lighting,
1280x720位的分辨率, 闪光灯
and dark sheets so you don't get a kick off the pillows.
暗色的床单 反光不会太严重
Took me a while to learn that little trick,huh?
我可是好长时间才琢磨出来了
These walls are completely soundproof.
这些墙壁是完全隔音的
You could scream your lungs out in here,
你可以在这里撕心裂肺的喊,
and nobody'd hear you.
－没人会听见
It's true.
是真的
so... anytime you wanna set up a shoot, just let me know.
所以... 什么时候你们想拍 告诉我就行了
You guys would love it.
你们会喜欢上它的
Once you get in front of that camera,
一旦你呆在摄像机前,
you feel like a star.
你会觉得你就是一个明星
good night.
晚安
Night.Night
晚安 晚安
I'm thinking no more play dates.
我再也不想要这样的玩伴了
Not a one.
一次也不要
Hey. We'd better hurry. The movie starts in 20 minutes.
嘿  我们最好快点 电影20分钟后就要开场了
There's been a slight change of plans.
计划有些小小的变动
My mother had a couple of friends
我妈妈有些朋友
who really wanted to meet you,
他们很想见你
and I thought,"what the heck?It could be fun." Do you mind?
我想“有什么好怕的? 会很有意思的” 你介意吗?
Uh,no,I-I guess not.
呃,不,我-我想不会.
Hey,everybody,this is bree.
嘿,大家好,这是bree.
- and this is my uncle sid.
- 这是我舅舅sid.
Hi.
你好
- My aunt rosalie.
- 我阿姨rosalie
hello
你好
Oh,and this is stan grazi,who does my mom's taxes.
哦,这是stan grazi,负责我妈妈的税金
She's a knockout,george.
她是那么引人注目,george.
Guess I owe you an apology.
我想我欠你一个道歉
Since I was single all these years,
因为这些年我都是单身,
stan kept telling my mom I was gay.
stan 一直跟我妈妈说我是个同性恋
I'm still gonna need some proof.
我还需要一些证据
But I guess I'll be getting that
但我想我可以得到证实
in about nine months,hey,bree?
在九个月内,对吗,bree?
What happens in nine months?
九个月内会发生什么?
That's just stan's little joke
那只是stan开的一个玩笑
about when we're gonna start our own family.
关于什么时候我们会有自己的家庭
Now just so you know,stan,
就像你所知道的,stan,
it's gonna be a while before we even think about kids.
考虑要孩子还是以后的事呢
I want bree all to myself for a while.
我想自己好好和bree独处一段时间
Well,don't wanna wait too long.
不需要等很久
After 40,the eggs don't get any fresher.
40岁以后,卵就不再有活力了
Am I right,bree?
我说的对吗,bree?
if you'll excuse me,I,uh,I have to go.
请原谅,我得走了
Bree,bree,where are you going?
Bree,bree,你要去哪?
I am taking my champagne and my aging eggs,
我带着我的香槟以及我的老卵
and I'm going home.
我要回家
What's wrong?
怎么了?
george,I'm starting to think that
george,我开始想
we made a mistake rushing into this engagement
我们这么快定婚是一个错误
- what?
- 什么?
And I'm not the only one who thinks that.
我并不是唯一一个这么想的
Other people have said the same thing
其他人也这么认为
What others? Andrew?
其他人是谁? Andrew?
No. Dr. Goldfine,my therapist.
不是 是我的心理医生Goldfine
Your therapist?He doesn't know me.
你的心理医生?他并不了解我
Well,he knows me,and certainly better than you do.
可是他了解我 很明显比你更了解
How can you say that?
你怎么能这么说?
Well,for starters,he knows the last thing
是的,从开始到现在,他知道每一件事
I'd ever want to do is have more children.
我从来都不想再要孩子
Really? Well,I didn't know.
真的? 可我并不知道
But you should know that.
你应该知道
That's the kind of thing that people who are engaged
这是定了婚的人
are supposed to know about each other.
彼此应该知道的事
Well,it doesn't matter.I don't need children.
这没关系,我不需要孩子
It's not just that,george.
并不仅仅是这些,george.
Dr. Goldfine has other concerns about us being together,
Goldfine 医生对我们 在一起还有其他一些疑虑
and I'm starting to think he's right.
我开始想他是对的
Look...
你看...
I'll agree with dr. Goldfine on one thing.
就一件事我跟Goldfine医生达成一致
We should slow things down.
我们应该把事情放慢些
Really?
真的?
Yes. Just because two people are engaged
是. 两个定了婚的人
doesn't mean they have to get married anytime soon.
并不意味着要马上结婚
I'll talk to dr. Goldfine about it tomorrow.
我明天会跟Goldfine医生谈谈
Take whatever time you need.
需要的时候就去吧
how many times am I gonna have to ask you to fix this step?
都跟你说了几次了,要修下这楼梯?
Matthew,are you going to answer me?
Matthew,怎么不回答我?
Did you leave the door open?
你是不是忘了关门了?
How'd you do?
你那边怎样?
Not good.
不妙
People are gonna start coming home from work soon.
他们就要下班回家了
Okay. We can't panic.Caleb is scared.
不要恐慌.Caleb已经吓到了
He doesn't know the area, so he's got to be close by.
他不熟悉这里 应该就在附近
Which yards haven't you checked yet?
哪些院子你还没找过?
Bree,I desperately need your help.
Bree,我十分需要你的帮助
Oh,dear. What's wrong?
哦 天那  怎么了?
How do you get your hydrangeas to look so stunning?
你是怎样做到让你的 水仙花看是去那么迷人?
I'm systematically slaughtering my own garden.
我非常系统性的清理我的花园
Do you really want to know my secret?
你真的想知道我的秘诀?
Oh,yes.
哦,是的
Horse manure.I have it delivered.
我给它施了马粪
Susan makes fun of me, but the proof is in the pudding.
Susan因此取笑我 但事实胜于雄辩
Hello.
你好
Hey.
嘿
Looking for something?
在找什么?
Ahem. Uh... yeah.Actually, I'm looking for you.
呃... 是的 事实上 我在找你
Me?
我?
You're looking for me?
你在找我?
Yeah. I've been thinking about you,
是的  我一直在挂念着你
and that time we met, I thought you were really cool.
自从我们上次见面以后, 我觉得你真的很不错
So you came to ask me out?
那么你是来约我出去?
'Cause I'll say yes.
因为我会答应
Thank you.
谢谢
Anything?
有吗?
well,that was a waste of time.
真是浪费时间
Pretty much.
是呀
did you hear the big news?
听到大新闻吗?
Uh,the big news?
呃,大新闻?
Karl and I are back together
Karl和我又和好了
What?
什么?
And I know that he stayed at your place last night,
我知道昨天晚上他在你那过夜了
which leads me to why I'm here.
这就是我来这的原因
There's some stuff that I have to say,
有些话我必须要说
and it's not going to be pleasant.
听起来会不怎么舒服
Edie,uh...
Edie,呃...
whatever it was that you said to him really helped.
无论你跟他说的是什么,很有效
He showed up with flowers and he apologized for everything
他带着花出现,为他所做的一切道歉
So...
所以...
thank you.
谢谢
I'm sorry,what?
不好意思,你说什么?
Well,I'm not gonna say it again.
我不会说第二次
It hurt my teeth the first time.
刚才就让我难以启齿了
No,edie. This is so unexpected on so many levels.
不,edie. 这真的让人出乎意料
I don't know what to say
我不知道该说什么
Then say nothing
那就什么都不别说
Oh,and,uh,here...
哦 这是...
is the photo of you I found in our bed.
在我们床上找到的你的照片
I know he told you about it.
我知道他跟你提过
Why are you giving itto me?
你为什么把它给我?
Look,I appreciate whatever it was that you did last night,
你看,我很感激昨天晚上你所做的一切
but it's still important for you to understand that...
但是你必须明白一件很重要的事是...
I won.
我还是赢了
You won?
你赢了?
Yeah. Whatever little hold you had on karl
是的 你跟karl之间的任何关系
is officially over.
都已经正式结束了
So you can stop feeling all smug
因此你不用再为他保留这张照片
and superior that he kept that... thing.
而感到得意或是有优越感
Believe me,I don't feel superior.
相信我，我没觉得优越
Good,'cause you shouldn'T.
很好 因为你根本就不应该
He made his choice,and it's not you.
他做了这个选择,他没选你
You're right.He made his choice.
你是对的 他做了选择
no,bree,it's still too easyto breathe.
不,bree,它还是太松了
You've gotta make it tighter.
你得把它弄得再紧点
Gaby,if I make it any tighter,
Gaby,如果再紧点,
you won't be able to sit down.
你就没法坐下了
I don't care.
我没关系
I can't have these girls thinking I'm pregnant.
我不能让这些女孩们知道我怀孕了
Gosh,do you actually think they're gonna make fun of you?
Gosh,你真的认为她们会嘲笑你?
Trust me. They're merciless.
相信我  她们很无情
But why? I mean,surely they have friends who have children.
可是 为什么? 我的意思是她们也有朋友作妈妈了啊
When I decided to marry carlos,
当我决定嫁给carlos的时候
I told these girls I would spend the rest of my days
我告诉这些女孩们,我的下半辈子将会是
being rich and in love and childless,
富有、充满爱和没有孩子的
and they laughed at me,
那时,她们取笑我
and they said I would just end up being another
她们说我最终将变成一个肥胖的主妇
fat hausfrau livinga life that I didn't plan.
过着我所不期望的生活
I'm not gonna give them the satisfaction
我不想让他们称心
of knowing they were right.
被她们说中
Well,maybe they'll just be happy for you.
也许她们只是替你感到开心
Bree,my friends are models. They're never happy for anyone.
Bree,我的朋友都是模特 她们从不为任何人感到开心
Do you ever thinkyou might like it?
你有没有想过也许你会喜欢?
What?
喜欢什么?
Motherhood.
做一个母亲
- No.
- 不
Oh,come on
哦,别这样
You don't think you're gonna love your own baby?
你就没想过你会喜欢你孩子?
Well,I'm not saying I'm not gonna grow attached to the little bugger
我不是说我对小家伙没感情
I just don't have the motherhood gene.
我就是没有母性基因
I wish I did,but I don'T.
我很希望有，可惜
what?
笑什么?
Well,I'm just smiling because I think a few months from now
我只是在笑，也许几个月后
you are gonna come to me
你会跑来跟我说
and tell me how madly in love you are with your
你疯狂的喜欢上了
new little baby,
你的小宝贝
and I'm gonna have to resist the urge to say "I told you so."
而我必须抵制住自己情绪 对你说“我早就料到了”
Maybe,but I doubt it
有可能,但我很怀疑
There you go. All done.
可以了　　完成
How do I look?
看上去如何?
Positively glowing.
光彩照人
Bree... aah!
Bree...
hi! Hello!
嘿! 你们好!
oh,my god!
哦 天啊
You're pregnant!
你怀孕了!
bree? It's gaby!
bree? 是gaby!
Honey,it's open.Come on in.
亲爱的,门开着　进来就是了
Hi. My,uh,friends just left,
嘿,我朋友刚离开
and I was hoping you could come over
我在等你过来
and cut me out of this thing.
帮我把它脱掉
How was your little reunion?
你的小聚会如何?
It was,um... weird.
有点...不可思议
Weird?
不可思议?
Well, allison's mad
是的, allison快疯了
because she's losing jobs to 14-year-olds,
因为她被一个14岁大的模特抢了饭碗
holly is on a strict diet of cruciferous vegetables,and...
holly正在吃一些花科类的植物 还有...
yasmin is undergoing a new embryonic facial treatment
yasmin 正在做一个新的脸部手术
that probably causesshort-term memory loss.
有可能会导致短期失忆
You know,I just stood there the whole night
你知道吗，整晚我就只是站在那里
trying to remember why we were ever friends.
想要记起为什么我们曾经会成为朋友
And I couldn'T.
但我不能
You know,honey,people change.
你知道，大家都在变
Yeah,but that's the thing. They haven't changed.
是的,问题是， 她们没变
That's who they've always been.
她们还是老样子
I've changed,and I honestly don't know how.
我已经变了,在不知觉中
maybe susan, lynette and I have had a good influence on you.
也许susan lynette 和我对你有了好影响
I doubt that.
我也觉得是
Come on.When I finish up here,
好了  等我把这里弄好
I will come over with my sewing kit
我会带着我的缝纫包过去的
and cut you out of that.
帮你把它脱掉
All right,but hurry up,
好的,不过快点,
because I've been having to pee since hors d'oeuvres.
因为从开胃小菜以后，我就想上厕所
are you free to go shopping tomorrow?
明天有空一起购物吗?
I figured it's probably time I...
我想是时候该...
bought some clothes that actually fit.
买一些真正合适的衣服了
Well,I know a store that carries maternity clothes
我知道有一家专卖孕妇装的店
with designer labels.
是名牌的
I like the sound of that.
我喜欢你那样说
Thanks.
多谢
thank you.
Yes,cameras are tools designed to capture images.
是的 照相机是用来捕捉画面的
Wait.
等等
What is it?
怎么了?
Uh,she needs me to get something for her.
呃,她要拿些东西
I will be right back.
我马上回来
But in truth,they can capture so much more.
可事实上,它能捕捉到更多东西
They can uncover hidden longing
它能揭示一个你从不在意的男人
of men who should no longer care.
心底隐藏的渴望
They can reveal the extraordinary secrets
它能泄露许多普通婚姻的
of the most ordinary marriages.
特殊秘密
Most amazing of all,
最惊人的是,
cameras can quietly and clearly reveal to us our dreams--
它可以在不知觉中告知我们--
dreams we didn't even know we had.
曾经从未拥有过的梦想
Desperate Housewives Season 2 Episode 7
-=COSL-YTET小组工作室=- 翻译: 少数派 Maggiezl 校对: 少数派 Ronald